So friends, let's start today's video
and first of all we are going to talk
about our index, Nifty 50,
because even today if you have seen, the
company, that is, the index,
set a new all-time high and broke the old high, so
you should know this thing too, and not just Nifty
50, if you look at Sensex, Bank,
Nifty, that is, all the indices, all are setting
new all-time highs and
breaking the old highs, so this should make you
understand whether our
market is continuously trading at an all-time high,
which is a very good thing,
and one thing you should know is whether tomorrow is going to be a
holiday, whether the market will be closed tomorrow,
otherwise you will get up and sit relying on everyday
and mean you will start watching the market, but
you will not see the market running, so for this
I have told you this thing also, and if we
talk further about Maruti's company, then a
very tremendous and excellent thing is coming to light
because if you look, you
can see that the company is going to increase its capacity
and you can see
in clear words that the company has said that the
company is going to increase its capacity.  It is going to
expand, yes
friends, you can see that the company is
going to expand its manufacturing
capability, so this is a very great thing
because I tell you that whenever any
company expands, does capex,
expands, then it is a very great and
excellent thing and it has a direct
impact on the revenue of the company and
if you manage the expenses then the
profit of the company is bound to increase and
this is a very good step taken by the company
but many people think that then
why does not every company do it, then there are
two-three reasons behind it, firstly, to
expand, capex costs
money, so this is the first thing
and the second thing is that even if you do
exponential capex, but there should be enough demand for it, otherwise
you will only
increase the supply but if there is
no demand then there will be no profit, so if both the
things happen then the expansion is very
great and the same company is going to do it
and you can see where, the company
which is in Manesar  The company has a plant where you
can see that the company already manufactures around 8 lakh
vehicles, so you can see there that the
company has increased its capacity
by 1 lakh vehicles and now the total capacity can be seen that the
company is going to manufacture 9 lakh vehicles per annum, so this is a
big step and a
good step of the company, you should also know this and if
you look, you
can see that it is located there, you can see that
Vitaran-Jabalpur,
we are also working towards the dream of the Government of India of self-reliant India and are
making only Made in India vehicles and not only this,
in the coming time we are going to
increase the capacity even more, that is, we are going to double it
in seven-eight years, so this was a very
big statement because if you see, then some
people may say why seven-eight
years, because for those who do not have any idea, let
me give you an idea, is the company
quite big, Maruti's a very big company,
from this you can guess, what do you mean, every
second vehicle that is sold in India
among four-wheeler passenger vehicles is Maruti's.  It is
so big that we can say that
their market share in India, so it will take
seven to eight years for them, that is, doubling the capacity in 7-8 years is
also a big thing which the
company has done and that is when any customer
goes, they give all these options, that is
if someone says we want the first, that
means buy a Swift, buy a Deezer,
buy a Swift, someone says our family is
big, then buy a Tigor, buy an XL6, that means they do
something or the other, that means they have
many different models in all the price ranges,
so this is a great thing
for the company and for such a big company to
double its manufacturing capacity in seven to eight years,
this can also be called a big milestone,
if the company really did this, then
you should know about this and the
latest news which I also know, can we say that it is
new right now,
which is the new price range, that is approximately if you
look at it,
in the
forty-seventh, you will see, then a lot can be said that both
foreign institutions and domestic
institutions have invested in mutual funds  You
can also say that you have invested a lot of money
in the company, that is, if you look at the last two-three, three-four
months, then
you should have an idea about this too. Now you will say that
they have bought it, then we will also buy it, so
this means that you should not make this mistake
because if you look at it, then they bought it
in the last two-three months and you have just come to
know about it, then it is possible that they will
also put it on sale now, that is, you will not even know
when they buy and when they sell, so you should
not make this mistake. And if you have
information about the company, if you have a
background, then it is good. If you do not
know, then you should also know
how much debt the company has,
what plan has the company made to repay the debt, what plan has the company
made, the company is going to demerge its business
into five different companies, so I
mean, you need all the information, only after that
you should take any decision whether to buy the shares of this company or
not because the
money is yours, so the choice will also be yours. And if we
talk further about ICICI Lord General
Insurance Company, then you know that it is an
insurance company, but along with that
you also know that it is an investment
company.  And if you look at the latest news
about the company, you can see that the
company has done an acquisition. If you look at State
Bank of India, yes friends,
if you look at SBI, then they have done an acquisition.
Acquisition does not mean they are buying the company, but
acquisition of shares means they are buying some stake in the company
because it is new, which means they are
investing something. And if you
want to read in detail, then you can read it. You can see
that their previous stake was at 0.05.
Now you can see that it has been acquired at 0.06. So
you should know this as well. Now you will say that
such a small stake is big but it also requires a
lot of money because
SBI is a very big company. So you should know about this as well.
If we talk further
about Turk company, then for those who do not know, let
me tell you that the company
works in the real estate sector and especially if you
look at Delhi Noida, that is, if you look at that segment, that is,
in that area, you will see that the
company has a big presence and
if you look at it, the company has said that
their new project, Turk Kailasa, you
can see that the response to the company was good.  It has been
received for that project, so
this is a very big thing, it is an excellent thing and you can
see that the company has got sales of Rs. 1400 crore from there.
Yes friends, the company has got sales of Rs. 1400 crore from
there, so this is a very big thing, it is an
excellent thing and that is why the company can
say that it has
achieved a big achievement. Now some of you
may ask what is so big about this, so let me
tell you that the
sales of Rs. 1400 crore by the company is a
big thing because
if you look at the market cap of the company, it is a small company, it
means the
market cap of the company is around Rs. 5000 crore and
if such a small company gets Rs. 1400 crore from a single project, then it is considered a very big
thing in the real estate segment,
so you should know this thing also and if
you look at it, you can see that the company has also
said that the project was a very
luxurious project and if you look at their
residences which are unsold and sold,
almost all of them are HN,
high network individuals.  There were big
entrepreneurs' projects, those were
luxurious projects, they had 3 and 4.5 BHK
luxury residences which the company
sold, so you should also know about this, so that's all for
now, thank you very much,
keep watching more such videos.